var questions = [{
	"question": "What is the fifth busiest U.S. airport ?",
	"option1": "CMH",
	"option2": "JFK",
	"option3": "CLE",
	"option4": "ATL",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "What is the oldest airport in operation in the U.S.?",
	"option1": "LAX",
	"option2": "DFW",
	"option3": "KCGS",
	"option4": "ATL",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "What year did commercial jet service begin ?",
	"option1": "1952",
	"option2": "1974",
	"option3": "1983",
	"option4": "1964",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
    "question": "Dulles Airport is named after a former U.S. Secretary of State ? What is his full name ?",
	"option1": "George Dulles",
	"option2": "Abraham Dulles",
	"option3": "Ian Bill Dulles",
	"option4": "John Foster Dulles",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
    "question": "During take‐off, the Boeing 767 sucks in enough air to fill the Goodyear Blimp in ____ seconds: ?",
	"option1": "15",
	"option2": "13",
	"option3": "7",
	"option4": "5",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
    "question": "What airline is the world’s largest purchaser of caviar, buying over 10 tons per yea ?",
	"option1": "Delta",
	"option2": "Lufthansa",
	"option3": "United Airlines",
	"option4": "British Airways",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "What airline invented business class in 1979?",
	"option1": "Qantas",
	"option2": "Lufthansa",
	"option3": "KLM",
	"option4": "British Airways",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "What is the oldest airline still operating under the same name?",
	"option1": "Qantas",
	"option2": "Lufthansa",
	"option3": "KLM",
	"option4": "British Airways",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "How many engines did the Howard Hughes H‐4 Hercules ‐ a.k.a. The Spruce Goose – have?",
	"option1": "12",
	"option2": "10",
	"option3": "8",
	"option4": "6",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "What is the second busiest U.S. airport?",
	"option1": "CMH",
	"option2": "LAX",
	"option3": "KLM",
	"option4": "JFK",
	"answer": "2"
}]